(Bernadette:)Thank you, Raj.
(Raj:)Please, this is my way
of thanking you
(Raj:)for letting me stay here.
(Raj:)Now, tell us all about your day.
Okay, well, first,
(Bernadette:)I was late to a meeting
because I was stuck in traffic.
(Howard:)I keep telling you to put
that traffic app on your phone.
(Raj:)Hey, when you got home today
complaining that you felt sick
(Raj:)from eating too many jelly beans,
did I tell you how to fix it?
(Sheldon:)No.
I said, "Aw, that must hurt,"
and I rubbed your belly.
(Howard:)I thought of you the whole time.
(Raj:)All I'm saying is
there's a time to just listen.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Raj:)There's also a time to stop
eating too many jelly beans.
(Raj:)And it's when you're ten.
(Sheldon:)Hello, President Siebert.
(Sheldon:)Thank you for taking my call.
(Sheldon:)I just wanted you to know
that you can now expect
(Sheldon:)enthusiastic participation
from me regarding my discovery.
(Sheldon:)No, no, no, no.
No need to thank me.